<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>chatGPT-Minecraft-Devlog-English</title>
    <link href="/2024/08/10/chatGPT-Minecraft-Devlog-English/"/>
    <url>/2024/08/10/chatGPT-Minecraft-Devlog-English/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Development Log: Elemental Alchemy - A New Minecraft Mod</p><ol><li><p>Introduction<br>Ever since I started playing Minecraft, I’ve been captivated by its limitless creativity and openness. As a mod developer, I’ve always wanted to add more content to the game, offering players new experiences and challenges. This time, I decided to develop a mod called “Elemental Alchemy,” which aims to introduce new magical elements and challenges to the game.</p></li><li><p>Initial Concept<br>The inspiration for this mod came from the classic concept of alchemy. I wanted players to explore the world, collect various elemental resources, and use alchemy to craft powerful magical items. My goal was to create a mod that seamlessly integrates with the vanilla Minecraft experience while providing new layers of fun and challenge.</p></li><li><p>Technical Choices<br>To bring this mod to life, I chose to use Minecraft Forge as the base framework for mod development. Forge offers a robust API and extensive documentation, making it easier to develop custom items, blocks, and entities. I also used IntelliJ IDEA as my development environment, alongside MCP (Minecraft Coder Pack) for decompiling and analyzing the game’s code.</p></li><li><p>Development Process<br>Key Challenges<br>One of the biggest challenges I faced during development was balancing the new elements with the vanilla game content. Alchemy involves introducing a lot of new resources and crafting recipes, which, if not carefully managed, could disrupt the game’s balance. To address this, I repeatedly adjusted the resource acquisition difficulty and recipe complexity, ensuring that players could gradually unlock powerful alchemical items.</p></li></ol><p>Major Milestones<br>Phase One: Implemented the basic alchemy system. Players can now combine different elemental resources on an alchemy table to craft various magical items.<br>Phase Two: Introduced elemental creatures. Each element has a unique guardian creature that players must defeat to obtain rare elemental cores.<br>Phase Three: Implemented the alchemical ritual system. By performing complex rituals at specific locations, players can summon powerful elemental bosses and harvest extremely rare materials.<br>Iterative Improvements<br>After the initial release of the mod, I received a lot of feedback from the community. Some players wanted more alchemy recipes, while others suggested adding more powerful boss fights. Based on this feedback, I added additional content in subsequent updates and fine-tuned the difficulty of the boss battles to enhance the overall gaming experience.</p><ol start="5"><li>Lessons Learned<br>Successes<br>The “Elemental Alchemy” mod successfully expanded Minecraft’s gameplay and was well-received by players. I’m particularly pleased with the design of the alchemy recipes and elemental creatures.</li></ol><p>Areas for Improvement<br>If I were to do it again, I would conduct more extensive testing in the early stages, especially concerning game balance. While players are generally satisfied with the mod, I realize that some recipes still need adjustment in terms of resource difficulty.</p><p>Development Insights<br>Throughout the development of this mod, I’ve come to appreciate the importance of community feedback. Players’ suggestions not only helped me identify issues but also provided valuable creative ideas for the mod’s further development.</p><ol start="6"><li><p>Next Steps<br>Looking ahead, I plan to add more types of elements and alchemical rituals to the mod. I’m also considering introducing multiplayer cooperative alchemical rituals, allowing players to work together to perform complex transmutations and unlock even more powerful magical forces.</p></li><li><p>Conclusion<br>The development of the “Elemental Alchemy” mod has been an exciting journey, not only expanding the possibilities of Minecraft but also pushing me to grow both technically and creatively. I’m very grateful for the community’s support and feedback, and I look forward to bringing more exciting content to everyone in the future.</p></li><li><p>Attachments<br>Code Example<br>java<br>复制代码<br>&#x2F;&#x2F; Example Code: Alchemy Table Crafting Recipe<br>GameRegistry.addRecipe(new ItemStack(ModItems.alchemyStone),<br> “ E “,<br> “SCS”,<br> “ E “,<br> ‘E’, ModItems.elementCore, ‘S’, Items.STICK, ‘C’, Blocks.COBBLESTONE);<br>Screenshot or Video Demonstration</p></li></ol>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>chatGPT</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>chatGPT-Minecraft-Devlog</title>
    <link href="/2024/08/10/chatGPT-Minecraft-Devlog/"/>
    <url>/2024/08/10/chatGPT-Minecraft-Devlog/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>开发日志：我的世界新模组——元素炼金术</p><ol><li><p>引言<br>自从我第一次接触《我的世界》（Minecraft）以来，我一直被它无尽的创造力和开放性所吸引。作为一名模组开发者，我一直希望能在游戏中加入更多的内容，让玩家们能够体验到全新的玩法。这次，我决定开发一个名为“元素炼金术”的模组，旨在为游戏增添新的挑战和魔法元素。</p></li><li><p>初期设想<br>模组的灵感来源于经典的炼金术概念，我希望玩家能够通过探索世界，收集各种元素资源，并通过炼金术合成强大的魔法物品。我的目标是让模组既能融入原版游戏的体验，又能为玩家提供新的乐趣和挑战。</p></li><li><p>技术选择<br>为了实现这个模组，我选择使用Minecraft Forge作为模组开发的基础框架。Forge提供了丰富的API和文档，使得开发自定义的物品、方块和生物变得更加容易。为了简化开发过程，我还使用了IntelliJ IDEA作为开发环境，并搭配使用了MCP（Minecraft Coder Pack）来进行代码的反编译和分析。</p></li><li><p>开发过程<br>关键挑战<br>在开发过程中，我遇到的最大挑战是如何平衡新元素与原版游戏内容之间的关系。炼金术需要涉及到大量的新资源和合成配方，如果不加以控制，可能会导致游戏体验失衡。为了解决这个问题，我反复调整了资源的获取难度和配方的复杂性，确保玩家能够循序渐进地解锁强大的炼金术物品。</p></li></ol><p>重要里程碑<br>第一阶段：实现了基础的炼金术系统。玩家可以在炼金台上组合不同的元素资源，合成出各种魔法物品。<br>第二阶段：添加了元素生物。每种元素都有其独特的守护生物，玩家必须打败它们才能获取稀有的元素核心。<br>第三阶段：实现了炼金仪式系统。通过在特定地点进行复杂的仪式，玩家可以召唤出强大的元素Boss，并从中获取极其稀有的材料。<br>迭代改进<br>在初版模组发布后，我收到了社区的热烈反馈。一些玩家希望增加更多的炼金配方，而另一些玩家则建议添加更强大的Boss战。基于这些反馈，我在后续版本中增加了更多的内容，并对Boss战的难度进行了优化，使得游戏体验更加丰富。</p><ol start="5"><li>学到的经验<br>成功之处<br>“元素炼金术”模组成功地扩展了《我的世界》的游戏玩法，并得到了玩家的积极反馈。特别是在炼金配方和元素生物的设计上，我感到非常满意。</li></ol><p>改进空间<br>如果再来一次，我会在早期阶段进行更广泛的测试，尤其是在平衡性上。虽然玩家对模组整体满意，但我意识到有些配方的获取难度仍需调整。</p><p>开发心得<br>在开发这个模组的过程中，我深刻体会到社区反馈的重要性。玩家的建议不仅帮助我发现了问题，还为模组的进一步发展提供了宝贵的创意。</p><ol start="6"><li><p>下一步计划<br>未来，我计划为模组添加更多的元素类型和炼金术式。此外，我还考虑引入多人合作的炼金仪式，允许玩家在一起进行复杂的合成，解锁更为强大的魔法力量。</p></li><li><p>结语<br>“元素炼金术”模组的开发是一次非常有趣的经历，不仅拓展了《我的世界》的可能性，也让我在技术和创意上都得到了提升。我非常感谢社区的支持和反馈，希望未来能为大家带来更多有趣的内容。</p></li><li><p>附件<br>代码示例<br>java<br>复制代码<br>&#x2F;&#x2F; 示例代码：炼金台合成配方<br>GameRegistry.addRecipe(new ItemStack(ModItems.alchemyStone),<br> “ E “,<br> “SCS”,<br> “ E “,<br> ‘E’, ModItems.elementCore, ‘S’, Items.STICK, ‘C’, Blocks.COBBLESTONE);<br>图片或视频演示</p></li></ol>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>chatGPT</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>chatGPT-ARGameTool-Devlog</title>
    <link href="/2024/08/10/chatGPT-ARGameTool-Devlog/"/>
    <url>/2024/08/10/chatGPT-ARGameTool-Devlog/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>开发日志：AR游戏地图编辑工具的诞生</p><ol><li><p>引言<br>在开发我们最新的AR游戏时，我们意识到玩家在游戏中创建和自定义自己的地图将大大增强他们的游戏体验。为此，我们决定开发一个专用的地图编辑工具，让玩家能够在真实世界的环境中构建和分享他们自己的AR游戏关卡。</p></li><li><p>初期设想<br>最初的灵感来自于经典的《我的世界》（Minecraft），我希望玩家可以像在那里那样，随心所欲地创建自己的游戏世界，但在这里，是通过手机的摄像头和AR技术实现的。目标是让工具直观易用，同时提供足够的灵活性，支持从简单的结构到复杂的建筑设计。</p></li><li><p>技术选择<br>为了确保地图编辑工具的性能和跨平台支持，我选择了使用Unity引擎，并搭配AR Foundation框架。这一选择得益于Unity在3D内容创建上的强大能力和AR Foundation对iOS和Android的支持。此外，为了简化UI设计，我还采用了Unity的UI Toolkit。</p></li><li><p>开发过程<br>关键挑战<br>在开发初期，我们遇到了一个重大挑战——如何确保玩家创建的3D对象能够准确地锚定在现实世界的物理位置上。经过多次尝试和调整，我们最终通过改进光学追踪算法，成功提升了AR锚点的稳定性。</p></li></ol><p>重要里程碑<br>第一阶段：成功实现了3D对象的创建和基础编辑功能。玩家可以通过简单的手势来放置、移动和缩放3D模型。<br>第二阶段：添加了环境识别功能，工具能够自动识别并适应周围的物理环境，避免出现穿模或浮空的情况。<br>第三阶段：实现了地图分享功能，玩家可以将他们的创作上传到云端，与其他玩家共享和下载。<br>迭代改进<br>工具的初版在内部测试中暴露了一些问题，特别是UI不够直观。经过几轮用户反馈，我们重新设计了UI布局，使工具更易于使用，同时添加了教程模式，帮助新手玩家快速上手。</p><ol start="5"><li>学到的经验<br>成功之处<br>我们的AR地图编辑工具在性能和用户体验上都达到了预期效果。特别是环境识别和锚定技术，使得玩家创建的地图在现实世界中具有极高的沉浸感。</li></ol><p>改进空间<br>回顾整个开发过程，我认为可以在早期阶段进行更多的用户研究，以避免后期对UI进行大规模的调整。此外，我们可以进一步优化云端同步功能，以提升地图加载的速度和稳定性。</p><p>开发心得<br>开发这个工具让我深入了解了AR技术在游戏中的应用潜力，也让我意识到用户体验的重要性。即便技术再先进，如果不能方便地为用户所用，也难以成功。</p><ol start="6"><li><p>下一步计划<br>未来，我们计划进一步优化工具的性能，减少对设备硬件的依赖。同时，我们正在探索将AI技术引入编辑工具中，让玩家可以通过简单的语音指令来创建和编辑地图。此外，我们也在考虑推出一套高级编辑功能，供有经验的玩家使用。</p></li><li><p>结语<br>AR地图编辑工具的开发是一个充满挑战但也非常令人兴奋的过程。这个工具不仅丰富了我们的游戏，也为玩家提供了更多创作的可能性。感谢整个团队的努力，以及早期测试玩家们的宝贵反馈。</p></li><li><p>附件<br>代码示例<br>csharp<br>复制代码<br>&#x2F;&#x2F; 示例代码：对象创建与放置功能<br>void PlaceObject(Vector3 position)<br>{<br> GameObject newObject &#x3D; Instantiate(prefab, position, Quaternion.identity);<br> ARAnchor anchor &#x3D; newObject.AddComponent<ARAnchor>();<br> &#x2F;&#x2F; 其他相关设置<br>}<br>图片或视频演示</p></li></ol><p>这个示例基于假设的情况，你可以根据实际情况调整内容。如果有具体的开发过程或想要展示的功能，我可以帮助你进一步完善。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>chatGPT</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>TIS</title>
    <link href="/2024/08/03/TIS/"/>
    <url>/2024/08/03/TIS/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>MinecraftDevlog</title>
    <link href="/2024/07/26/MinecraftDevlog/"/>
    <url>/2024/07/26/MinecraftDevlog/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Devlog</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>MinecraftDevlog</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>testPaper</title>
    <link href="/2024/07/23/testPaper/"/>
    <url>/2024/07/23/testPaper/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>this is a test paper</p><p><img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/LostPromise0710/PictureStorage/img/img/anon.jpg" alt="anon"></p><p><img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/LostPromise0710/PictureStorage/img/img/mygo.jpg" alt="mygo!!!!!"></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>test</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>test</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello World</title>
    <link href="/2024/07/23/hello-world/"/>
    <url>/2024/07/23/hello-world/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to <a href="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</a>! This is your very first post. Check <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/">documentation</a> for more info. If you get any problems when using Hexo, you can find the answer in <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/troubleshooting.html">troubleshooting</a> or you can ask me on <a href="https://github.com/hexojs/hexo/issues">GitHub</a>.</p><h2 id="Quick-Start"><a href="#Quick-Start" class="headerlink" title="Quick Start"></a>Quick Start</h2><h3 id="Create-a-new-post"><a href="#Create-a-new-post" class="headerlink" title="Create a new post"></a>Create a new post</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo new <span class="string">&quot;My New Post&quot;</span></span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/writing.html">Writing</a></p><h3 id="Run-server"><a href="#Run-server" class="headerlink" title="Run server"></a>Run server</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo server</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/server.html">Server</a></p><h3 id="Generate-static-files"><a href="#Generate-static-files" class="headerlink" title="Generate static files"></a>Generate static files</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo generate</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/generating.html">Generating</a></p><h3 id="Deploy-to-remote-sites"><a href="#Deploy-to-remote-sites" class="headerlink" title="Deploy to remote sites"></a>Deploy to remote sites</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo deploy</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/one-command-deployment.html">Deployment</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
